Ning,
if you want to visit the lantern festival,
Ying'er can accompany you.
Ying'er can also
ride horses, shoot arrows,
drink, and roll dice.
I can keep you company in all of these.
Catfights, catfights,
nothing but catfights.
I'm really out of ideas.
Watch out for the carriage!
My Lady!
Ning Yuanci, you dodge quite fast.
I was almost knocked over.
Are you all right?
How does it feel
to stand up?
Why are you standing up?
Go back and sit down right now.
It is exactly as I guessed.
You were faking
your crippled leg.
You are truly shrewd, General.
So all of this
was to test me.
Last time you fell into the lake,
no one pushed you.
You jumped in yourself.
Was this poisoning
premeditated too?
She...
Her legs only recovered
after taking the royal medicine you sent.
It truly is a medical miracle.
I had no choice but to fake my lameness.
As for the poisoning,
I am as curious as the General
about who did it.
If the General doesn't believe me,
do with me
as you please.
What use do I have
for your life?
True.
If I die,
you won't have a hostage
to threaten my father.
Ning,
don't you still need to investigate
the poisoning?
Catching the culprit is more important.
It's getting late.
You should go back now.
It seems
I should carefully reconsider
the marriage contract.
Better keep him away
from Xue Ruowan.
Trouble will brew if they keep talking.
Good thing Ning Yuanci didn't dwell on
your fake limp.
He even said he would reconsider
the marriage.
It seems
your freedom is just around the corner.
Even though I don't want to marry him,
I don't want you
to keep tangling with him either.
Didn't you say yourself
that he's a
scumbag?
Are you really going
to keep engaging with him?
I
only curried favor with him
to help you
and clear my own name.
Who wants to tangle with him?
That's good.
No.
Is she playing
some new kind of female rivalry with me?
My Lady,
you haven't fully recovered.
Why must you come out
to meet the Second Young Lady?
What if you catch a cold in the wind?
I haven't been out
for a long time.
If I don't use these legs,
they will actually go lame.
Besides,
Keying asked to meet me.
Will the Second Miss
ask you out just to set you up
and trick you
like before?
She has risked her life
to save me three times,
and even kept my secret
of pretending to be lame.
I doubt she has any intention
of harming me.
Do not make
such assumptions about her anymore.
But
I am afraid she might leak your plan
of faking your death
to escape the marriage.
So,
we must not say this outside,
lest others hear it.
Then, My Lady,
will you marry Ning Yuanci?
Of course not.
I just need
to find the right time
to get out of it.
But I am worried about you.
You worry about this
and that every day.
Aren't you tired?
I am not tired.
I am willing to serve you
for the rest of my life,
My Lady.
Once I get out of this,
I will find a way to buy your freedom.
Then,
you won't have to be anyone's maid.
You can do
what you want
and live the life you like.
But My Lady...
All right.
If you really find
this lantern festival boring,
go back to the residence
and keep an eye on my father.
Don't let him find out I sneaked out.
Lanterns.
Young Master Chu,
Wan,
Your
leg is healed.
That girl Xue Keying
is playing tricks on me again.
Lady Keying
wouldn't lie.
Does she have something
to discuss with us?
I think
she just wants
to be a puppy.
Why don't we
stroll around
and look for her nearby?
The Magpie Bridge Lantern Festival.
Such a romantic atmosphere.
The male and female leads...
You guys should take this opportunity
to speed things up.
Hurry up and get together
so I can reach the finale
as soon as possible.
Miss, take a look.
Look at this piece.
This color suits you best.
General.
You mean Xue Shiyan...
Where would he hide
the deer totem?
Cui Hu,
I'll leave you to your work.
All right.
What on earth is this?
Wan, what are you looking at?
I think
I heard Keying's voice.
General Ning,
You hold a high position
and must have
many official duties.
Why are you following me around all day?
I do have many official duties.
But I am more curious about
how many faces you have.
What act are you
putting on this time?
I...
But bringing me here
did remind me of something.
What is it?
Don't you know you should ask
for a girl's permission
before kissing her?
You didn't ask for my permission
when you kissed me last time.
When was that?
Right here.
Last July...
This Xue Keying...
She's good for nothing
but throwing herself at men.
Anyway,
even for the 100th time,
you have to ask for my permission
before kissing me.
I've done no less than
a hundred kissing scenes.
You think I'd be manipulated
by a fictional character?
Where did Xue Ruowan go?
This Xue Keying is really something,
asking us out
Stop!
and we can't even find her.
Don't run!
Miss Xue.
What is it?
General,
There was a suspicious merchant
holding something.
But I lost track of him.
Please forgive my incompetence.
Pass on my orders. Close the city gates
and carefully inspect
everyone leaving the city.
Xue Ruowan,
are you alright?
Where did you go?
Mr. Chu and I
looked for you for a long time.
Don't even mention it.
I just ran into a dog on the way.
It blocked my way
and even bit me.
Where did it bite you?
Why didn't you dodge?
I couldn't dodge it.
Why is your face so red?
I just ran,
so I'm a bit hot.
You really are something.
You asked Mr. Chu and me out,
but you disappeared.
You also invited them?
You also invited him?
I...
I.
This is
an abandoned entertainment house,
which I have already purchased.
I plan to open
an immersive theater themed
around painting and calligraphy.
This is
the reason I invited you
and Young Master Chu out.
Theater